V minulých dílech Warehouse 13...
A už ten meè ukradl kdokoli,
tak má i další vìci, které patøí Skladišti.
Což znamená, že máme konkurenci.
Lattimer a Beringová, že?
Jsou tak syroví, tak netrénování, tak zkorumpovatelní.
A co vaši?
Colorado Springs.
Mají tam knihkupectví jménem Bering & synové.
No, musí na tebe být pyšný.
Vidìls nìkdy ten film Velký Santini?
To s tím pøísným otcema vydìšenýma dìckama?
Bylo to tak zlý, co?
Jo, až na to, že to neskonèilo za dvì hodiny.
Colorado City, COLORADO
No páni.
Berlin, NÌMECKO
- Myko? - Artie, jsem tady.
V MacPhersonovì bytì.
Myko, buï opatrná.
Macpherson je pryè. Další slepá ulièka.
Našel jsem ho!
Pete mìl v Montréalu víc štìstí.
Jak víc štìstí?
MacPherson míøí na východ do Sainte-Catherine!
Artie, jdou po mnì poldové!
- Poldù se zbavím, jdi dál po MacPhersonovi.
- Napravo je ulièka. Míøí k metru.
Pozor všem jednotkám.
Zrušte pronásledování v Sainte-Catherine!
Spadá to do kompetence Královské kanadské jízní policie!
Opakuji: Spadá to pod KKJP!
Máme ho, Artie!
Buï opatrný, Pete. Nevíme, jestli je má.
Artie.
Vzdej to, MacPhersone. Tentokrát jsme tì dostali.
Artie, má ten èinel. Má ten èinel!
Pete, musíš odtama vypadnout! Prostì padej odtama!
Když uvidíš èinely, zakryj si uš...
- Pete? Artie? Co se stalo? Je všechno v poøádku?
Pete! Pete, slyšíš mì?
Pete!
...už víckrát ne...
Pete. Hele, Pete. Pete, musíš vstát.
Mami, jsem vzhùru. Nepøijdu pozdì.
Jsem v pohodì. Stihl jsem si zakrýt uši.
Kde je? Kde je MacPherson?
Je pryè, Artie.
Ztratil jsem ho. Ztratil jsem MacPhersona.
Hele, mami, poslyš. Zrovna teï nemám èas.
- Vážnì nemùžu... - Myko, jde o tátu.
Zaèalo mù být špatnì a já... já... on... on...
Co?
Prostì pøijï domù. Proste se vra. Prostì pøijï domù.
Musíme to tu zabalit.
Artie, potøebuju domù.
Jedu domù, mùj táta umírá.
No ty vole!
Ví Tamara že ji pronásleduješ?
Nebo jenom chceš okoukat, jak se nalíèit?
Vra mi to, Gregu.
Nerozbreè se, blbeèku.
No, já nevím, Leeno. Je to složité.
MacPherson na nás líèí volavky a falešné stopy...
má je po celém svìtì
a mùj software to dokázal zúžit jen na dvì místa
a Montréal se ukázal jako, chápeš,
ten, který... øíkalas, že nechceš žádný ledo do li...
Bože! Nedìlejte to!
Paní Fredericová, co jste provedla s Leenou?
Promiòte. Nedala... nedala byste si li... li... Ne.
Jste tady, protože chcete vìdìt, co se stalo.
Dva mrtví policisté. Vím, co se stalo.
FIX_ME The montreal police have
a dashboard camera in the car. dashboard camera = kamera na palubovce, snima to z pohledu ridce? vyraz?
Ale to jsem Petovi øekl, nahrávku má on.
- Jak jste... - Prosím tì.
Podívejte se, sledovali jsme stopu.
Støílel jsi od boku.
Zasáhli jsme støed terèe.
Malorážní kulkou.
Pete má velkorážní kulky. My...
Víte co? Tahle analogie už staèila.
Mìli jsme dohodu.
Mìl jsi získat informace...
- Já vím.
- Pøínést je mì...
- Jo.
- A my bychom naplánováli...
spoleèný postup proti MacPhersonovi.
Nemìl jsi žádnou ofenzivní strategii.
Žádné obranné postavení. Žádný záložní plán.
Nebyl jsi pøipravený.
Kde jsou Lattimer a Beringová?
Pryè.
Spravuj mùj majetek lépe nebo pøísahám pøi popelu
pùvodních 12 skladiš, že jej dám pryè.
- Zase MacPhersona dostanu. - O tom nepochybuji.
Nepodnikneš proti nìmu žádné kroky, aniž bys je nejdøív se mnou konzultoval.
Ano, madam.
Máte...?
Jak to dìlá?
Dobrá, vážení.
Prosím, zavøete své sešity, dámy a pánové.
Tamaro, mohla bys je, prosím, posbírat?
Tedy dobrá. "Na východ od ráje" od Johna Steinbecka.
Zrada, ztracená láska, žárlivost. Dobré ètení.
Prosím, pøeètìte si prvních 50 stran, zítra si udìláme diskuzi.
Když budete té lásky. Pøíjemné poètení.
Bobby, mùžeš na okamžik?
Jsi v poøádku? Zdál ses mi trošku roztìkaný.
Úkol do výpoèetky. Ponocoval jsem.
Už... už jsi s ní mluvil?
Nìco pro tebe mám.
- Díky, Tamaro. - Není zaè.
Poezie. Burns, Blake, Byron.
A to je jenom B.
Nech je, a mluví za tebe, hm?
Hodnì štìstí.
Mami.
Mami?
- Mami. - Ach, Myko.
Ahoj, ahoj! Tvùj telefon nefunguje...
- ...a já ti volala, ale.... - Vybila se mi baterka.
- Kde je? - Je v poøádku, neboj.
Je nahoøe, proè se za ním nejdeš nahoru podívat?
Je mi líto, že jsem tì vydìsila, ale už je v poøádku.
- Ahoj. - Ahoj.
- Jo. Výlet nadarmo, holka.
Vzala sis sem zbraò?
- Jo je zabalená dole. Rozebraná.
Myslela jsem, že budeš v nemocnici.
- Myslela jsem, že umíráš. - Tvoje matka pøehánìla.
Jsem v poøádku.
- To nebyla mrtvice? - Ne, ne, ne, žádná mrtvice.
Udìlali mu pár dalších testù, ale Bože!
Mìlas ho slyšet køièet.
- Já nekøièel.
- Ale.
Celý svùj život jsem nekøièel!
Pamatuješ si, co se stalo?
Ne, nepamatuju se nic. Akorát, že jsem se vzbudil
v sanitce a øíkal si, co se to kèertu asi dìje.
- Jeannie, udìlej holce nìco k jídlu. - Mami, já... já nemám hlad.
To protože tvoje chu k jídlu umøela hlady.
Hm, doktor øíkal, že by to mohl být virus.
Seš moc hubená.
Nìco s vnitøním uchem nebo zánìt páteøe.
Hm, dali mu steroidy a antiviriotika.
Paní B., jé, èau.
Budu potøebovat recept. Tahle pálivá omáèka je super.
Výbornì. Ó, máte tady trochu...
Kouknìte se na sebe. - Ó, pardon.
Co tady...?
- No, Peta už známe. - Páni, to je otrapa.
Právì jsem pøijel, poznal tvého tátu.
Ty jsou vaše? Našel jsem je v kuchyni.
Jo, velice se omlouvám. Ty jsou na...
sbírání dùkazù, promiòte.
Co tady dìláš?
No, napadlo mì, že bys mohla potøebovat podporu.
Artie disagreed
but was overruled.
Kým?
Mnou, otrapou.
No, nepotøebuju žádnou podporu.
Hm... sleèna Nezávislá. Já taky ne.
Vážnì, tati. Jsem tu, jak dlouho?
- Minutu?
- A taky sleèna Netykavka.
Prosím tì, Warrene.
Musím jít dolù do sklepa.
Snìz nìco!
Nemám hlad.
No, pùjdu pøipravit pokoj pro hosty.
A pro tvoji postel mám nové flanelové povleèení.
Koupila jsem ho u Dodyho. Ne, ne, ne. Jste mými hosty.
Je to mùj dùm. Jste mými hosty.
Páni.
A co práce?
Hm, no práce zmizla.
A než se zase objeví, tak jsem tady jako pøítel.
FIX_ME In this hopefully
not too stressful time.
FIX_ME I mean, it could have
been worse, right? your dad?
Díky.
Vážnì, já... oceòuju to. Máš pravdu.
Mohlo to být horší.
- well, hey, wait, wait.
myka, myka, myka.
- yeah?
- look, i was talking
to your dad.
He thinks you're still in d.c.
they both do.
- well, yeah.
And if you tell them
any differently, i swear,
I will--i will drop a dictionary
on your crotch.
What? i'm supposed to tell them
that i'm working
for the world's most dangerous
antiques roadshow?
- no.
you tell them the truth.
Or at least
part of the truth.
I don't know. something
to cut the stress.
- i'm not stressed.
- you're lying to them.
- it's a force of habit,
you know?
It keeps my dad from being
disappointed.
You have hot sauce
all over your face.
[eerie whispering]
- [screams]
- dad!
Mom?
- myka, get back.
- dad?
- watch your eyes.
- oh!
[electricity crackles]
- warren. warren.
What happened?
- what happened is...
Your dad's got an artifact.
- myka!
Myka! hey!
- where's the notebook?
- it's this way.
- myka?
- mom, it's okay.
- myka, who is it?
is she--
- this is claudia.
we work with her.
- what's that?
- that is--
- claudia, back here.
- that's for me.
- no, you wait
just a minute.
I want some answers,
myka.
Now, first of all, who is
the man in the little tv?
- his name is artie.
- and is he a doctor?
- no, but--
- your father belongs
in a hospital.
- this isn't medical. mom,
this is something else.
- and how do you know?
you're not a doctor.
You protect the president.
- not anymore.
I'm still with the government,
but i am doing this now.
- what?
what are you doing?
- i'm trying to help dad, mom,
so just let me do that.
Trust me.
please.
- ready?
- yeah.
Um, mom, just stay here.
Whatever you see or hear,
just stay put.
- but--
- just don't move.
- do--
- it'll be okay.
They do this kind of stuff
all the time, so--
- claudia?
- i gotta--
- but what's going on?
- they're really good
at this.
- [groans]
- here it is.
- kill it.
- duck and cover.
- what's happening?
- mom, how's dad?
- um, he's the same.
Why, was something
supposed to happen?
- check his arms.
- it's still there.
- it's ink.
ink.
Take it out.
- now what?
- the neutralizer failed
Because i think we're dealing
with a bifurcated object.
It's--it's got
at least two parts,
And they're each dependent
on the other.
And, uh, that notebook is just
one half of the package.
- so what's the other half?
- you know, based on
the manifestations of the ink,
Then that would tell me that
it's a pen,
Most like--well, a pen,
anyway.
Oh, by the way,
the shipper's address?
That's completely phony.
- macpherson sent it,
didn't he?
- [sighs]
i don't know that.
- so what?
he's coming after family now?
- what does he want?
- well, he wants to hurt us,
Because we're going after him.
- stop, stop, stop, stop.
Just stop it. we don't know
who sent it or why.
If it is macpherson,
it could be revenge or mischief
Or a diversion
so that we're doing this
While he's doing
something else.
Just in case,
just to be safe, i've, uh--
I'm circling the wagons
around joshua
And around pete's family.
Who or why does not matter.
What matters is your father
and the notebook.
Now--now, listen.
I've analyzed the text.
it ain't good. it's poe.
Um, edgar allan poe.
The reason that the book is
getting under your father's skin
Is because the pen
is not with it.
- so, what? we bring the pen
together with the notebook
And this all stops?
- yeah.
Well, probably,
If it follows a typical
bifurcated artifact scenario.
It can't be an accident
That this book found its way
to your dad.
Look, uh, myka, right now
your father is a conduit.
The notebook, the pen, they're
linked through his energy,
Through his love
of the written word.
- so where is this pen?
- well, i'm searching for
coinciding incidents right now.
Uh, you know, i've got
the filters off.
- but it's causing trouble
somewhere?
- but i'll find it.
you'll get it.
The next time he has an attack,
i'll trace the pen.
You'll retrieve it and reunite
it with the notebook.
- how long does he have?
- i don't know what you--
how long--what?
- how long does he have?
Artie, my father can't
take this much longer.
- um...
[stutters]
A day.
maybe two.
But you can help him.
Until i land on something,
myka,
Just surround him with
his books, with his world,
And read to him, myka,
read to him books that he loves
And use those words to fight
what's happening to him.
And just try to keep him
connected to reality if you can.
- bobby's not that bad.
- look, all i'm saying is,
watch out.
[both laugh]
Geek love. ugh!
- "i might have been improved
for my whole life.
"i might have been made
another creature, perhaps,
For life, by a kind word,
at that season..."
- do you
want me to take over?
- no, no.
i'm--i'm fine.
He's gonna be okay, mom.
DELETE_ME_LATER
Oh.
I'll be back in a sec.
I'm just gonna
take these dishes.
- freak's probably
swiped your panties
From gym class
or something.
- gross!
- tiger.
- dad?
- tiger, stop it.
- fire.
- dad?
- fire!
[all screaming]
- dad?
[screaming]
Help, somebody get some help.
- artie's got something.
- what?
- at the precise moment
your dad was shouting "fire,"
A kid in portland, oregon,
was burned
By some bizarre wall of flame
shooting from his locker.
No one can explain it.
- well, what about
the tiger thing?
- kid's a football star
for the kingford tigers.
- let's go.
- wait, myka.
I need you to stay here.
- i have to help my dad,
pete.
- i know, but we've got
two artifacts.
He's connected to one.
I need you to stay
on the notebook.
I'll take care of the pen.
Myka, look at me.
No one can help your dad
right now more than you can.
- i can't let you
go alone.
- i'll take claudia.
- keep her safe.
- yeah.
But there's something else.
- what?
- i think i'm hot
for your mom.
- i'll break it to dad.
- okay.
- i needed to speak
with you, bobby.
Is, uh--
is everything okay?
The poetry inspiring you?
- not so much.
- you know, it seems
We had a little burglary here
the other day.
The story is that
it was one of the pens
That edgar allan poe used.
- oh, he used it.
Don't look at me
like that.
- i noticed that you were
fascinated with the pen.
- are you saying
i took it?
Are you saying i took it?
- i'll tell you what.
I'm gonna go to the lounge
for a soda,
And if the pen
should show up while i'm gone,
Well, we'll just chalk it up
To something strange
and mysterious.
Back in a bit.
- mr. ives.
mr. ives.
Here.
- "wall"?
"wall"?
"wall" what?
- you.
[eerie whispering]
- [screaming]
- [moaning]
The youg man ########################### football
??????????????????????????
##################
??????????????????????????????,,
- really?
does he like horror novels?
Stephen king,
lovecraft, poe?
- you're assuming the boy reads.
no, he's just a bully.
Look, i mean, how big
a deal is this?
I mean, this school's got
a reputation to maintain,
And if it gets out
That the government's
investigating a teenage prank,
It'll put a lot
of parents off.
- you mean donors?
- why do you think
it's just a prank?
- well, we're not schooling
little terrorists here.
Somebody in the science class
got tired
Of parmut picking on him
and gave him a hotfoot.
- oh, yeah?
how's he doing?
- he's fine.
uh, you want this open?
- no. we'll, uh,
we'll take it from here.
- you'll want to step back,
please.
- why?
it's not dangerous.
- please.
Thank you.
Okay.
you ready?
- why not?
- okay, we're in business.
here we go.
So, uh, you had
any other incidents?
- with what, fire?
- well, anything strange.
Say a tell-tale heart,
perhaps?
- what?
- there you go.
- gotta love artie.
- what's that?
- you don't happen to have
Edgar allan poe's pen
lying around, would you?
- well, actually--
- yes?
- mr. ives' classroom.
He likes to collect items
from famous people.
- the pen is here, then.
- well, it was.
um, it got stolen.
- [murmurs]
- this last one
was the worst.
- i know.
- [murmuring]
- dad?
- if you'd been a boy
i'd have called you sue.
- what?
- johnny cash.
it's a song.
a boy named sue.
- okay.
- make you tough.
- well, i'm sorry
i wasn't a boy.
- i'm sorry
i wasn't a father.
[groans]
- he has regrets.
- about me?
- yes.
About his life.
- what do you mean?
- he wanted to write books.
- i know. i know that
he wanted to write books.
- did you know
he wrote a novel?
- no.
- 12 times.
over and over again.
Unpublished.
He loved it too much
to let it go.
He was afraid.
- where is it?
- a long time ago,
when he finally gave up...
[exhales]
he told me to burn it.
He hasn't written a thing
since.
- [moans]
It can't be.
- mr. ives?
Hello?
- nice place for a pen,
soaking up all that poe juice.
- huh.
- do you know that ravens
are actually brilliant?
They've adapted to humans
like rats and cockroaches.
They've figured out how to
figure us out.
- shh.
- what?
Hear anything?
- just the beating
of my hideous--
- stop it.
- okay.
- listen.
[faint scratching]
What is that?
- a rat in the wall?
- short story.
- guy walled up.
- the cask...
- ...of amontillado.
- here, take if off there.
- i don't--
I don't want avian flu!
- take it!
- all right!
what do i--uhh!
- [grunting]
- [coughs]
- mr. ives?
- [grunting]
Who did this to you?
- [coughs]
bobby.
[coughs]
find him. stop him.
[creaking]
- bobby, not cool.
- myka, something's wrong.
- artie, i need help.
- what's this?
- a poem.
i wrote it for you.
- i gotta go.
- [groans]
- we're losing him.
- myka, just read to him.
- read it.
- i have read. i've read him
everything, okay?
It's not working.
- [anguished cry]
- you have to find the words
that he loves.
You have to find a book
that means more to him
Than--than anything
in the world.
- mom, tell me
you didn't burn it.
- what?
- dad's book.
- aunt cindy's bureau.
the bottom drawer.
- okay,
so ives said that--
That bobby had a crush
on what--what's her name?
- tamara.
- tamara, right.
There's always a girl.
- don't blame her.
blame testosterone.
Crazy, crazy man hormone.
- i'm not blaming the girl.
i'm blaming poe.
Bobby?
- crazy,
scary man hormone.
- check out
miss teenage zombie.
Oh, right.
Uh...
[clears throat]
Bobby...and...
- tamara.
- tamara, was it?
right?
[clears throat]
That's a nice pen,
bobby.
Why don't you give it up,
huh?
Come on, give it here.
- "pendulum"?
- you've gotta be kidding me.
- [gasps]
- bobby!
- i got it.
- bobby, you've got to
stop this.
I know,
you're all full of poe,
Up to your creepy eyeballs
in "nevermore" and crap, but--
- but--but--but
this isn't fiction!
It's real!
- it's the most real i have
ever felt in my entire life.
- the blue willow sky
by warren bering.
Chapter one.
"when the girl was born,
his first thought was fear."
- it's beautiful.
- bobby, you're a good person,
but you're--
You're hurting people!
You're hurting yourself
and you're hurting tamara,
And it has to stop!
- people like you
don't see me.
You don't believe in me.
People like you need to be
shocked into seeing.
You need to be horrified.
then you'll understand.
- understand what, bobby?
tell me what!
- that words have power.
- "...for her.
for his daughter.
She was his life."
[echoing]
- but this isn't fiction!
It's real!
- "she was his life.
His only job now
was keeping her safe."
- [moaning]
- "she was his life."
- it's working, myka.
[echoing]
- words have power.
- something's happening.
Go, go, claudia!
get the pen!
- who are you? what?
- one second. nice, claud.
- here's the bag.
- get him to a hospital.
this still has a hold on him!
And Micah's dad.
- myka! i got it. hey.
- hey.
- how is he?
- is that it?
- that's it.
- well, he--he's not worse,
But he's not better.
not--not completely.
- his strength
is the only thing
That's keeping that pen from
flipping completely out.
- okay, the notebook's
in place.
- good. take the pen,
keep it in the bag,
And just, you know,
approach the notebook.
- i'm on it.
- be careful!
- i am! would you stop
yelling at me?
Somebody turn down his volume
or something.
- okay. now what?
- you know, put the bag
right over the notebook,
Turn it upside down,
dump the pen out,
Make sure it lands on the
notebook and stays there.
- that's it?
just dump it out?
- yeah.
- just lay it on the notebook?
this isn't cirque du soleil!
Just dump the pen on the book
and stand back!
- all right!
- artie,
nothing's happening.
- uh, that's--that's okay.
it's all right, it's fine.
It's been a while
since they've been together.
Probably they're just
getting reacquainted.
[electrical buzzing]
- wait, wait.
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
- dad?
- [moaning]
[exhales]
What's this?
- [gasps]
Hi.
- what, did i doze off?
- um, sort of.
- i was dreaming
you were reading and...
You didn't burn it?
- no.
[laughter]
- i-i did.
- [laughs]
- okay, well, um,
i think i've got everything.
- honey?
- yeah.
Hey, i don't know what it is
you do for a living,
But you do it very well,
and i mean that.
I'll see you soon,
and we'll--we'll talk.
We'll talk about something
other than books.
- oh, mom.
- good-bye, honey.
thank you so much.
And, um,
you take care of pete.
- i always do.
- hello.
- got everything?
- yeah.
- called the cab? n--
- no, no. no, i didn't.
- oh.
- i think, mr. poe,
that when your things arrive,
We'll stick them in--yeah.
the madrid section.
That is if leena agrees.
- arthur?
Pete and myka
are in colorado springs.
- yeah, i know.
i should have tried--
- and so is macpherson.
[computer beeps]
- what?
how did he--
He was there
the whole time?
- he had us all distracted.
I think that was
macpherson's intent.
[farnsworth buzzing]
- ooh.
I'll take the farnsworth.
- good choice.
- mm-hmm.
Hey, artie,
we're heading home.
- myka! myka, listen!
myka!
- that was weird.
- hold on.
- vibe?
- huge.
your dad.
- what?
Is this poe? are we back
into the poe thing again?
- i don't know.
- you two are good.
I see why mrs. frederic
drafted you.
- ah-ah! i kill this, and it's
lights out for mom and dad.
- you hurt my father.
- he glimpsed the mind
Of one of the greatest authors
in the world.
He'll thank me later.
- oh, you'll be dead later.
- what do you want?
- i want what you risked
your lives to get.
I would have done it myself,
but i lacked the means.
You have
until the count of one.
- you came after family.
- arthur started it.
- what is that
supposed to mean?
- ask him.
- pete.
Now let them go.
Do it!
- thank you.
- consider it a loan.
- [gasps]
- what the hell was that?
- jack the ripper's
lantern.
- at least we know
where that is now.
Sync by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- he used us
from the very beginning.
- no. he used me.